{
    "id": "f857e6e00399422184cdb3a91a32d93d",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Somebody …………………………. at the door.",
            "description": "Use the present continuous to talk about an ongoing situation. ",
            "answers": [
                "waits",
                "is waiting",
                "has waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14de3de15b354494af6c9e2cf7914742"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. to submit the assignment by Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "supposed",
                "are supposed",
                "have supposed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5fd6419111a4175a515ac25e2a2c977"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. to be a scientist.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about likes, needs, wants and desires. ",
            "answers": [
                "aspires",
                "is aspiring",
                "has aspired"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e99bd3edf8484ccda03defe083b2afd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………………… yesterday.",
            "description": "Use the simple past to talk about finished events. ",
            "answers": [
                "rained",
                "has rained",
                "had rained"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "017bdde9a81e42deae9202ad0dc300b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… a strange experience the other day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "782bf276f90c453ab3d503c2de330549"
        },
        {
            "question": "The winners ………………………………… at the town hall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "felicitated",
                "have felicitated",
                "were felicitated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9d3cb564af34995a26601941cdef287"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news of his death ……………………………… us all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was shocked",
                "shocked",
                "have shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7c14ea7b98142a2b42115933915ae89"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother ………………………………. to hear from her son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "relieved",
                "was relieved",
                "has relieved"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b26e2da4967b4ccbae747ebebbf604e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "God …………………………. those who help themselves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "helps",
                "is helping",
                "helped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f53118475c424047848c5a153965e520"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam …………………………… a living by selling second hand goods.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "is making",
                "makes",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3294c077f8484906a46312cce31b3307"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ……………………………… for the holidays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "are waiting",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0879fddd0a41420088feda8f8127fac3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………………… absent since yesterday.",
            "description": "Use the present perfect to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8ad2acfc7e34dd4a3d568f8aeb25de1"
        }
    ]
}